

# **Profile**

Dedicated and result-oriented software engineer with 2+ years of experience in understanding and anticipating the agile infrastructure needs and creating an environment where development, quality assurance, staging & production work can proceed efficiently and securely.

# **Employment History**

#### Full Stack Web Developer, GeoCloud, New York City, USA

DECEMBER 2021

- Building of a uGeo website using reactjs and styled-components
- Development of an application using reactjs using apollo-client as state management to consume graphql endpoint.
- Conversion and building of User interface design on figma into fully fledged application using reactjs, apollo client and styled-components.
- Ensure writing code with best practises.

#### Associate Software Engineer, Decagon, Lagos, Nigeria

JUNE 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

- Solid understanding of frontend web development frameworks (Reactjs and Vue)
- Handled and developed UI design for e-commerce applications.
- Worked with other developers to implement database schema design using Postgres with Django for a meetup app.
- A member of a team that built an hotel management system
- Built an API using Django Rest Framework and Django for an e-commerce platform.

#### Frontend & UI Developer, JVC Computers, Port Harcourt, Nigeria

JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

- Improved and worked on existing codebases
- Collaborated with other software engineers to implement UI designs
- Responsible for designing and delivering technical content to students, in a structured, self-learning approach, while reinforcing, evaluating knowledge.

#### Frontend Developer, Pepcoders, Port Harcourt, Nigeria

JULY 2020 - DECEMBER 2021

- Developed new features and user interface from wireframe models
- Responsible for building UI designs into full-fledged applications using javascript frameworks(Vue, Nuxt)
- Worked with project managers, developers and customers to resolve technical issues.
- Developed the concept of technical solutions based on customer needs to ensure satisfaction.

#### Frontend Developer (Intern), Meghee, Port Harcourt, Nigeria

AUGUST 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

- Participated in the development of frontend design and projects
- Worked as Coding Instructor for Meghee Academy

#### **Details**

09132717758

ayesorofemi@gmail.com

## Links

LinkedIn

Github

**PortFolio** 

#### Skills

React

Nextjs

JavaScript

SQL

Django

Vuejs

Python

Git

Tailwindcss

HTML & CSS

Docker

Firebase

Figma

**Typescript** 

Postgresql

#### **Hobbies**

Reading

# **Education**

Mining Engineering, Federal University of Technology Akure,

NOVEMBER 2011 - OCTOBER 2017

**Certification, Scrum Fundaments Certification(SFC)** 

APRIL 2021 - MAY 2021

Credential ID: 849894

Software Engineer, Decagon Institute of Software Engineering, Lagos, Nigeria

JULY 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

#### **BOUNCER E-COMMERCE APPLICATION:**

NOVEMBER 2021

An e-commerce application to purchase gadget online Technologies Used - React js, Styled components, React slick.

## STRIDES RECRUITMENT AGENCY(INSURANCE COMPANY):

MAY 2021

A Site for an Insurance recruitment agency and included is their services page and contact page. **Technologies Used** - Bootstrap and Javascript